

Omorian Clifford

Omorian.c@gmail.com

Groningen

0630259433 17/01/2002



linkedin.com/in/omorianclifford https://www.omorianclifford.com/

Profile:

An ambitious game development graduate with a desire to break into the software development industry.

I am motivated to keep improving my skills and to learn new skills, both inside and outside of the industry, and often look for the next thing to learn the ropes of.

Having knowledge of both programming and sound design, I have often worked on multiple sides of a game development project, which led me to acquire skills in multiple areas.

Education:

Parcival College: VMBO-TL / MAVO; 2014 – 2019. | Completed.

Noorderpoort: Software Developer Games; 2019 - 2023 | Completed.

Skills:

- Unity Game Engine
- Sound Design & Music Composition
- Basic 3D Modeling
- Basic Web Development

Work Experience

Junior Developer Internship | Sfinx Games, Groningen | Sept 2022 - Feb 2023

- Programmed in C# for a game project in Unity.
- Tested several projects while documenting bugs and points of improvement.
- Improved the atmosphere of an existing project by designing fitting sounds.
- Composed two soundtracks for two different games.

Junior Developer Internship | Moyosa Media, Groningen | April 2023 – July 2023

- Developed multiple applications in Unity and C#.
- Developed part of a Web-AR application in Babylon|S and JavaScript.
- Tested several applications to find bugs or points of improvement.

Extra-curricular Experience:

Global Game Jam:

I have taken part in each edition of the Global Game Jam since 2020, during which I constructed the atmosphere for the games by composing soundtracks and sound effects, as well as assisting in programming where needed.